http://www.epowerdoc.com/policies/

EDIS Solutions for Hospital Emergency Departments
EDIS Solutions for Freestanding Emergency Centers & Urgent Care
EDIS Solutions for Microhospitals
Paper Templates
Physician Charting
Nurse Charting (NursingDoc)
Telemedicine
Discharge Instructions
Patient Tracking
E-Prescribing (EPOWERx)
About this Privacy Statement
EPOWERdoc has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: http://www.epowerdoc.com.
Kinds of Information We Collect From Our Customers
The personally identifiable information we collect is used to facilitate delivery of products and/or services to our customers. In the process of providing these products and/or services, we require our customers to provide certain personally identifiable information. If a customer sends us personal correspondence, such as e-mails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.
How We Use the Information We Collect
We internally use personally identifiable information about our customers to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and provide better service to our customers. We may occasionally use a customer's e-mail address and, in some situations mailing address or phone number, to contact a customer regarding administrative matters or notices. We may use information in the file we maintain about a customer to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.
Disclosure of Your Information
We respect the privacy of our customers and, therefore, we will not sell or otherwise intentionally release any of our customers' personal information to any third party. We will, however, cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries. We will disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials when required to do so in order to comply with a court order or to cooperate with law enforcement officials in the conduct of a criminal investigation.
Removing Your Personal Information
Customers always have the option of removing their contact information from our databases if they decide they no longer wish to receive future communications or to participate in any other part of our service. To do so, simply contact EPOWERdoc, 506 S. 93rd Street, Omaha, NE 68114, 515.965.8040  .
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. However, please keep in mind that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or believe that EPOWERdoc has acted in a manner inconsistent with this privacy statement, you may contact: EPOWERdoc, 506 S. 93rd Street, Omaha, NE 68114, 515.965.8040.
EPOWERdoc reserves the right to amend this privacy statement at any time, without notice, and only the current privacy statement may be deemed effective.
We appreciate your questions and comments. Thank you for visiting our Web site.
06/10/16
© 2020 EPOWERdoc. All rights reserved.
